[{"answer": "Oh, yes, absolutely.", "docId": "110907pmt", "aSentId": 82, "question": "Can it compete with China anymore?", "qSentId": 81}, {"answer": "I agree with every word you just said, Piers, including \"and\" and \"the.\"", "docId": "110907pmt", "aSentId": 111, "question": "What do you think?", "qSentId": 110}, {"answer": "Well, I'm very much in the second category.", "docId": "110907pmt", "aSentId": 168, "question": "Where do you sit?", "qSentId": 167}, {"answer": "You know what's so funny about this, Piers, I mean, when you think of all these oil companies giving millions and millions of dollars in donations to buy basically every politician to deny climate change, and then you have the politicians complaining about some poor tenured scientist who probably is struggling filling out 100 forms to maybe get a $25,000 grant over 10 years from the National Science Foundation.", "docId": "110907pmt", "aSentId": 254, "question": "What do you think of that?", "qSentId": 253}, {"answer": "I'm sure it's possible.", "docId": "110907pmt", "aSentId": 277, "question": "Yes, when you see, as I say, Rick Perry how espouse that nonsense as you put it, and he's way ahead in these polls to be Republican nominee, could you actually imagine a scenario where either he or one of the other Tea Party candidates is chosen as the person to take on Barack Obama in the next election?", "qSentId": 276}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110907pmt", "aSentId": 312, "question": "Does Barack Obama have it in him to beat his chest with this jobs speech, re-energize America, galvanize the people, and maybe carve the initials \"B.O.\" into the White House wall in a few months' time, yes or no?", "qSentId": 311}, {"answer": "I'm very good.", "docId": "110907pmt", "aSentId": 329, "question": "How are you, Piers?", "qSentId": 328}, {"answer": "I think it's really important.", "docId": "110907pmt", "aSentId": 336, "question": "How important do you think this speech is tomorrow, in terms of whether he will or will not be re-elected?", "qSentId": 335}, {"answer": "It's easy for the richest man in the country to advocate that.", "docId": "110907pmt", "aSentId": 362, "question": "What would you say to that, given that Warren Buffett, one of the richest men in the country, has advocated it?", "qSentId": 361}, {"answer": "Well, you know, over the last three or four days, I've seen many people put up little signs and the charts showing that at this point, four years ago, I was ahead and Hillary Clinton was ahead.", "docId": "110907pmt", "aSentId": 404, "question": "Is it a curse when this happens to any candidate, do you think?", "qSentId": 403}, {"answer": "I haven't ruled it out.", "docId": "110907pmt", "aSentId": 433, "question": "But have you ruled it out?", "qSentId": 432}, {"answer": "The situation is that two airplanes have attacked apparently -- what -- all right, well then let's go -- let's go north then.", "docId": "110907pmt", "aSentId": 461, "question": "Mayor, what's the situation right now?", "qSentId": 460}, {"answer": "Well, it is very emotional.", "docId": "110907pmt", "aSentId": 470, "question": "What are your thoughts as we head towards the day?", "qSentId": 469}, {"answer": "I'll be there.", "docId": "110907pmt", "aSentId": 501, "question": "Where will you be, Rudy, on the tenth anniversary?", "qSentId": 500}]